emorywheel.com 2007-12-03

# Privacy Policy | The Emory Wheel

The statement discloses the privacy policy of the Emory Wheel’s online edition, emorywheel.com. The Wheel created this policy to demonstrate its commitment to the reasonable privacy expectations of our users, both readers and advertisers. 

These guidelines are subject to change. If it is necessary to alter any components of this policy, The Wheel will immediately post the changes online. 

This site collects first name, last name, email address, user name and password for all registered users. IP addresses are also collected (the location of your computer on the Internet). Interactive features such as letters to the editor, polls, blogs, contests and surveys may require the user to provide more detailed personal information such as address, city, state, zip code and phone number. 

Emorywheel.com, like most Internet sites, uses “cookies” to enhance the user’s online experience. Cookies are short pieces of data used by web servers to help identify web users. If you are concerned about being identified or about having your web browsing traced through the use of a cookie, set your browser to not accept cookies. Please note that blocking all cookies prevents some online services from working. 

Emorywheel.com does not share, sell, trade, rent or give to other parties any information users of our site provide us. 

Emorywheel.com does not “spam” users and it is not our policy to send unsolicited email. As a registered user, however, you are requesting and will receive an email update of headlines with links back to our website with the publication of each print edition of the Emory Wheel. 

Emorywheel.com may contain links to other websites and is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other sites. We suggest you consult these sites for their specific privacy policies. 

Emorywheel.com uses a third party vendor to manage our classified advertising sales (Universal Advertising). This vendor collects more detailed information for processing classified advertising transactions. Universal Advertising’s privacy policy can be accessed at <http://www.universaladvertising.com/index.cfm> by selecting “privacy statement”. 

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this policy, please contact us at <http://www.emorywheel.com/about/contact.php> and select “general comment” for your correspondence. 

| 

Most Read

Most Read

Latest

Latest

Most Commented

Most Commented
